http://www.horseracegame.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy covers the site https://www.HorseRaceGame.com. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose the following information. By visiting and participating at HorseRaceGame.com you agree to the terms of this privacy policy.
Information Collection and Use
Information is collected for the purpose of processing transactions, contacting the user in conjunction with participation, enhancing the site, providing product offerings, offering tailored content, and maintaining a secure site.
A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), computer information (computer and browser information), content (email content and bulletin board postings), interactive data (account activity and searches performed), location data (current physical location), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), purchase information (purchase payment method and other purchase information), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), unique identifiers (login id or other id), computer information (computer and browser information), content (email content and bulletin board postings), financial information (financial account status and activity), interactive data (account activity and searches performed), location data (current physical location), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), online contact information (email address), physical contact information (physical address and phone number), purchase information (purchase payment method and other purchase information), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), unique identifiers (login id or other id), search terms (search text), transaction information (account transactions), user's name, user's birthdate, user's login information, user's home contact information, user's business contact information, 3rd party name, 3rd party birthdate, 3rd party home contact information and 3rd party business contact information. We retain this information as seen fit by our business practices.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates.
A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following the directions of the internet browser being used. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny cookies. Our web site uses cookies to enhance our site and our required to be able to login.
How Information is Obtained on a User
Virtual Sports, Inc. uses multiple methods and technologies for obtaining information on a user while a user is at a web site owned by Virtual Sports, Inc. This includes requesting information directly from the user, using cookies and session variables to track a user, and analyzing browsing activity of a user.
Sharing Information - Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.
Personally Identifiable Information
Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties. Personally identifiable information is information that identifies a specific person. It includes a person's name, address, telephone number, credit card number, and government-issued identification number.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
Aggregate information can be shared with any third parties. Non-personally identifiable information is every kind of information except for personal information.
Data Security
Virtual Sports, Inc. has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology for all sensitive financial or health data transmitted on our site.
Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information
If a user's personally identifiable information changes such as zip code, phone, email or postal address the information can be updated online. If a user wishes to correct/update information not updateable online or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.
Links and Advertisements
Our web site contains links to other sites. We may partner with or have special relationships with third party companies. We, Virtual Sports, Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites accessible through links from our web site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information that they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Our web site may also contain ad services. These ad services may contain data collection processes for providing such things as relevant ads. Virtual Sports, Inc. is not responsible for the data collection process of these ad services. Virtual Sports, Inc. is also not responsible for any ads, data, or information transferred to a visitor through these ad services. The collection process and the transfer of data and information of the ad service is the sole repsonsibility of the ad service. Virtual Sports, Inc. will not directly provide personally identifiable information to these services.
Changes to the Privacy Statement
The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it but if you continue to use the site with a new privacy policy in effect you agree to
be bound by the new privacy policy and all previous submitted information.
Data Retention Statement
We keep information about you and your purchases for as long as you remain our customer and will continue to retain this data for as long as we see fit.
Contact Information
You can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy through the following link: Contact Us.
Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes
If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, we can be contacted through the following link: Contact Us.
Home | About Us | Contact Us | Privacy Policy | User Agreement
Contact us and we will explain why our customers say this is the best of the horse racing games. Copyright © 2006-2020 HorseRaceGame.com. All rights reserved.
